非准确重复定时器(Alarm)虽然比准确重复定时器要好一些，
Inexact repeating alarms. Infinitely better than exact repeating alarms, but
但是它仍然不是理想的。任何类型的重复定时器的问题是
still far from ideal. The problem with any kind of repeating
它仍然是轮询服务器来检查更新
alarm is that it's still polling your server to check
所以你轮询的越频繁
for updates. So the more frequently you poll, the fresher the
你获得的数据也更新，但是电池损耗就越厉害
data you can display, but the higher the cost in
你可以为了节省电量减缓轮询的频率
battery life. You can pull as frequently to conserve battery but
但这意味着你获取的数据内容过时的更快
that just means your content will be stale for longer.
你也可以让用户决定自己更新频率
You could just let the user decide the update frequency themselves,
但这样做的话，程序就不再那么充满魔力了
but then you lose the magic. If only there was
是否可以有更好的方式呢？
a better way. Is such a thing possible? Yes it
是的。谷歌云存储消息让您的服务器可以
is. Google cloud messaging lets your server notify your app
在有数据需要下载的时候直接通知应用程序
directly when there's data ready to be downloaded. Or it
甚至它本身可以将新数据放入信息负载中
can even include the new data in the message payload
使用谷歌云存储消息,您可以通过谷歌的云
itself. Using Google Cloud Messaging, you can send messages from
从您的服务器上发送消息到安装了你的应用程序的设备上
your server to any installed instance of your app via
这样一来，你可以不用轮询了
the Google Cloud. As a result, you can stop polling,
这就立竿见影的提高了电池续航，也提升了
which will immediately improve battery life and also improve the
你的应用内容的新鲜度。同时，
freshness of your app. And instead, rely on your server
依赖服务器通知客户端的方式。
notifying clients when there's data to sync. These messages can
这些消息可以非常简单，只触发同步适配器
be simple tickles, that trigger a sync adapter by notifying your
来通知应用程序有新数据或需要下载
app that there is new data or need to download.
也可以将新数据放入消息的负载中发送出去。
Or you can include the new data within the message payload.
在sunshine这个例子里，我们使用了其它的服务器
In the sunshine example, we're using someone else's server. But
但即便如此，创建自己的中间层监听数据变化
even then, it may make sense to create your own middle
来通知已安装的应用程序实例也是很有意义的
tier that pulls the source and notifies your installed app instances
现在我们不会在这节课中设置一个服务器
when it notices a change. Now we're not going to set up a
但是你可以从开发者指南的教程网站上
server in this lesson, but you can see the full details for
看到使用谷歌云存储消息传递的全部细节
using Google cloud messaging from the developer guide linked to instructor nets.